<resources>
    <string name="app_name">My Botany</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <!-- Strings used for fragments for navigation -->
    <string name="first_fragment_label">First Fragment</string>
    <string name="second_fragment_label">Second Fragment</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="previous">Previous</string>

    <string name="hello_first_fragment">Hello first fragment</string>
    <string name="hello_second_fragment">Hello second fragment. Arg: %1$s</string>
    <string name="back_Button">back</string>

    <string-array name="plant_names">
        <item>Giant Dioon (Dioon spinulosum)</item>
        <item>Rose (Rosa 'Violet's Pride')</item>
        <item>Euphorbia (Euphorbia ephedromorpha)</item>
        <item>Dutch Hyacinth (Hyacinthus orientalis 'Splendid Cornelia')</item>
        <item>Alpinia purpurata 'Rosea'</item>
        <item>Tall Bearded Iris (Iris 'Argosy')</item>
        <item>Mammillarias (Mammillaria)</item>
        <item>Rubber Plant (Ficus elastica)</item>
        <item>Living Stones (Lithops lesliei)</item>
        <item>Peperomia</item>
        <item>Chinese Evergreen</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="plant_info">
        <item>This species of Cycad has left fossils up to about 170 million years ago. It is native to
            the limestone cliffs and rocky hillsides of the tropical rain forests of Veracruz and Oaxaca,
            Mexico. It is one of the tallest cycads left in the world to about 36 feet high. Its huge,
            compound, palm-like leaves have 120 to 240 leaflets armed with small marginal teeth. The
            female plants bear huge cones to 30 inches long and weighing up to 30 pounds, and contain up
            to about 300 seeds that are dispersed when the cones burst open. The plant can tolerate
            temperatures down to 28 degrees Fahrenheit. The tree lives several hundred years. It is
            easy to grow in tropical landscapes and likes full sun to part-shade and moist,
            well-drained soils. Even though they look like palm trees, Cycads are more closely related
            to Conifers by their cone reproductive structures.</item>
        <item>This is the most productive and prettiest rose in most gardens.
            It's subtly fragrant and blooms from late March until November. Grows up to 5 feet tall.</item>
        <item>A forgotten succulent Euphorbia from Guatemala, this species is related to Euphorbia
            guiengola. A very floriferous species, it can produce up to 500 flowers a year. Has similar
            care to most winter dormant species of Euphorbia, although it needs more humidity and water.</item>
        <item>The bud colors are beautifully shaded in light blue to lavender with tinges of violet.
            They take up little space. They're well suited to growing under the canopy of deciduous
            shrubs, in the area that's too shady and dry in summer for most plants. The hyacinth foliage
            dies back after flowering and isn't seen again til next spring.</item>
        <item>This herbaceous plant is native to the islands of the South Pacific. It sends up leafy
            cane-like stems arising from rhizomes that get 3 to 15 feet high. There are dwarf cultivars
            of this. The flowers are harvested as cut flowers in Hawaii.</item>
        <item>The most commonly found garden iris is the bearded German Iris (I. germanica) and its
            numerous cultivars. Tall Bearded Iris begin blooming in early May in most parts of the US,
            and continue through mid-June, depending on weather. Tall Bearded Iris range in height from
            28" to 48"! Modern hybrids of the Tall Bearded Iris carry wonderful combinations of color,
            form and bloom habits. </item>
        <item>One of the largest and most popular genre of cacti, known for flowering in profusion in
            crowns near the top of the plant. Generally well behaved in containers, provided excellent
            drainage, strong light, and discipline with the watering can. These are dry growing plants
            and they do not enjoy wet feet or low light. From North America and the Caribbean, just into
            South America. About 90% of the species are endemic to (found only in) Mexico, and a third
            of the species are endemic to a single state in Mexico. The two main hotspots are central
            Mexico and southern Baja California A defining feature of this genus (which is not unique
            to it) is the presence of dimorphic areoles. The spines come out at the end of the
            tubercles, but the flowers, bristles, wool, and branches (if present) all come from the
            axils in between the tubercles. Another defining feature is that flowers do not appear at
            the apex (top center) but just below it, typically in a ring below recently produced
            tubercles. Several Mammillarias make edible fruit, though some are much better than others.
            This genus, which recently absorbed the monotypic genus Mammilloydia, is apparently sister
            to Cochemiea, a group of hooked-spine plants with distinctive red, zygomorphic flowers
            attracting hummingbirds. Until recently Cochemiea was lumped with Mammillaria. However a
            recent (2021) revision of these genera based on DNA analysis rearranged them significantly,
            moving almost all the plants with hooked spines into the resurrected Cochemiea and leaving
            the straight-spined plants in Mammillaria. These changes do not seem to be widely accepted
            yet. These genera are cousins of the mostly North American Coryphantha and Escobaria, which
            bear their flowers at the apex.</item>
        <item>One of the most common and well-known house plants here in the northern USA. However,
            it is native to much of southern tropical Asia where it can grow to be a big tree to 100
            feet high with a big trunk with high buttresses. It is known as having an aggressive root
            system as a big outdoor tree.</item>
        <item>Flowering is usually an indication the plant is preparing for its water rest and watering should begin to be reduced.
            A pollinated seed pod will form a capsule that looks like a pentagon flower shape and will
            gradually dry to a brown color. It is closed when dry, but if water is placed on it, it will
            open out to release some of the seeds. If no rain or watering is present.</item>
        <item>Peperomias are a diverse group of small, easy-care houseplants with waxy and often highly
            textured leaves. Some of our favorite varieties include ripple peperomia, watermelon peperomia,
            baby rubber plant, and silverleaf peperomia. Its waxy, colorful foliage adds a splash of
            color in any room without taking up a lot of space.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="plantWaterInfo">
        <item>Dioon edule needs 0.8 cups of water every 9 days when it doesn't get direct sunlight and
            is potted in a 5.0" pot.</item>
        <item>Newly planted roses – water every two or three days. Established roses – water once or
            twice a week as needed to keep the soil moist around your roses.</item>
        <item>Water your euphorbia every two weeks in the summer time, but triple check that the soil
            is completely dry between each watering. When watering make sure the water is drainage
            through its growers nursery pot.</item>
        <item>Watering hyacinth about once a month with 1 inch of water when rain is lacking
            is all that is generally necessary.</item>
        <item>Summer 1-2 times a week. The substrate must be wet.</item>
        <item>Water deeply once every week or two during the dry spring and summer months</item>
        <item>You should only water about once a month, and then quite sparingly. Just give
            the plant enough water to prevent having it shrivel up</item>
        <item>Water every 1-2 weeks, allowing soil to dry out between waterings. Increase frequency with
            increased light.</item>
        <item>Water living stone plants every two to three weeks, or when the soil dries out, between May
            and July, which is when living stones are actively growing. Soak the soil until water runs
            out of the bottom of the pot at each watering. Don't water again until the soil is completely
            dry.</item>
        <item>Water every 1-2 weeks, allowing the potting soil to dry out between waterings. Expect to
            water more often when your cactus is in brighter light and less often in lower light.</item>
    </string-array>

    <array name="plant_images">
        <item>@id/fillerImage</item>
    </array>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

</resources>